[{"answer": "You'll to have to ask him.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say any incriminating things that will go to make it harder to kind of make peace.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "It's pretty sad, because obviously he's an intelligent guy.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What was your reaction today when he finally resigned?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I was surprised that he did it, frankly, to begin with.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Were you surprised by the tone of it?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yes, I do feel vindicated.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Andrew Breitbart, I mean, do you feel vindicated today and do you have any sympathy for Anthony Weiner?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, there's several questions there.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "How do they best deal with this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "No, you don't.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "I'm not sure about the same enthusiasm, but I probably would have gone after him.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "I mean, Andrew, if you had the same information right now -- and for all I know, you may well do -- on one of your own, a Republican, would you have gone after him with the same enthusiasm?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I think it has caused damage to the Democrats because in these three weeks, they were really thinking they had a little roll going on Medicare, spending and other issues, taxes.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "And how much damage has it caused, if any?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Do I think it's a good idea?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "I want my $200.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Will you quiet down?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I'm well.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Tatum, how are you?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Like I've always thought you were part of our family.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you have an overwhelming sense of relief -- both of you, do you think, that at least you manage to get back to somewhere, even if it's not perfect yet?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "'NEAL: I felt like I would be there for him because it's Father's Day and a day our show launches.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "How did you feel when he asked you over for Father's Day?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Have you watched it together yet?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I don't really think about that.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "When you see that, do you wish sometime you had never been pushed into that world?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Do you still watch it?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, with my daughter.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Let's focus on you.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "About him?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "'NEAL: I would say 98 percent.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "How much of the drugs played a part in the down side of your life?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "They were round.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "How did you get them?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "First pot.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "And what was the drug?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "You'll have to ask him.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say incriminating things that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace and have healing.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Obviously, like you showed, the arrest.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "The one when you felt most ashamed?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Through a friend, a person after my divorce.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "How did you get into heroin?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Do you still call them friend?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I feel good about myself.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "And what do you think?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Thank you for saying that.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How can this be the crazy Tatum O'Neal?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I know I'm winning the battle.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Do you think you're winning the battle?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I've been sober for a year now.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "How long have you been clean now?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Like beyond.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Are you proud of yourself?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "You should be proud.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "So how could I not be proud?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "First, it is really sad, because he was a really -- kind of an ambitious -- really ambitious, up and coming congressman, who wanted to be mayor.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "First, what's your view of Weiner-Gate and (INAUDIBLE), really?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Do you recognize that kind of self-destruct button?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "There are so many different ways now.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What's the best way for any addict to try and deal with it once this has all been blown up like it has?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "For me, a 12 step program worked for me.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "What did you find was the best way?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I know it is saving my life a day at a time, for sure.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Did it save your life?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Amazing.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "How do you physically feel these days?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Not even a little bit.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Do you miss drugs?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I'm grateful.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Are you surprised at that?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Did you ever get mad at her?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "One of the most beautiful women in the world, of course.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "And I was looking at her pictures and thinking, gosh, how I am a going to compete?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Just that one that I write about in my book, where I went to talk to her while she knew she was sick in her apartment, and got to kind of talk to her.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Did you have any real relationship with her for a long time?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Was she sorry to you for what had happened?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "'NEAL: Well, I think so.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Do you think she was the love of your dad's life?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Well, if you know my dad, and you'll get to meet him, you'll sort of see that he is just always joking and stuff.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "The word awkward could have been invented for that moment.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Is he basically just an incurable romantic, do you think, your dad?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "You're so right.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "He loves women?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Twenty two.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Do you know how old I was when I married him?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "This was a guy smashing rackets and shouting \"you cannot be serious\".", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "So do you think I had like the full idea of what I was doing in my life?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "We get on as well as a divorced couple who have three grown kids can.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "How do you get on these days?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Do you talk regularly?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Do you talk to your ex-wife regularly?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Maybe two.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Six years ago?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "Two years ago?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "Mine.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "Whose decision was it to end the marriage?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "Not well.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "How did he take that?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't have any love life.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "What's your love life like these days?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "Zero.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Zero?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "No, I'm really not.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Are you looking for a man?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "Maybe a gentle, smart, loving person.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "What kind of man do you think now you ought to be with?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "110616pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "Wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 743}]